<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Carberry</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="login_now">Login now</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot password</string>
    <string name="welcome_back_to_carberry">Welcome back to Carberry!</string>
    <string name="refund_policy">Refund policy</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of service</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="password_hidden">Password hidden</string>
    <string name="password_shown">Password shown</string>
    <string name="do_not_have_account">Don’t have account?</string>
    <string name="create_one">Create one</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_description">Enter email address associated with your account and we’ll send an email with instructions to reset your password</string>
    <string name="create_new_password">Create new password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New password</string>
    <string name="confirm_new_password">Confirm new password</string>
    <string name="refund_description">You pay for the work that we do, not for the result of that labour. Any work we do or any time we spent must be paid for, for this reason not possible refund. Only if really solution not work then we can do for this order status "close" and then amount for this order will go on your account in our system for using it for next orders. You do not have the right to discuss our modifications made in the tuning file by us, otherwise the administrator has the right to block your account. If user selected wrong ECU in order, administrator will write about wrong selection in ticket for exact order and will notice about prices changes because of wrong ECU was selected. And if in selected priority time client not accepting that, admin have rights to finish order with correct selection orders options and prices.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_overview_description">This application is operated by CB (Carberry). CB offers this application, including all information and services available from this application to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here.\nBy visiting our application and/or purchasing something from us, you engage in our “Service” and agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions (“Terms of Service”, “Terms”), including those additional terms and conditions and policies referenced herein. These Terms of Service apply  to all users of the application, including without limitation users who are vendors, customers, merchants, and/or contributors of content.\nPlease read these Terms of Service carefully before accessing or using our application. By accessing or using any part of the application, you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this agreement, then you may not access the application or use any services. If these Terms of Service are considered an offer, acceptance is expressly limited to these Terms of Service.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_online_store_terms">1 - Online Store Terms</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_online_store_terms_description">By agreeing to these Terms of Service, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.\nYou may not use our products for any illegal or unauthorized purpose nor may you, in the use of the Service, violate any laws in your jurisdiction (including but not limited to copyright laws).\nYou must not transmit any worms or viruses or any code of a destructive nature.\nA breach or violation of any of the Terms will result in an immediate termination of your Services.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_general_conditions">2 - General Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_general_conditions_description">We reserve the right to refuse service to anyone for any reason at any time.\nYou understand that your content (not including credit card information), may be transferred unencrypted and involve (a) transmissions over various networks; and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices. Credit card information is always encrypted during transfer over networks.\nYou agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit any portion of the Service, use of the Service, or access to the Service through which the service is provided, without express written permission by us.\nThe headings used in this agreement are included for convenience only and will not limit or otherwise affect these Terms.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_accuracy">3 - Accuracy, Completeness and Timeliness of Information</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_accuracy_description">We are not responsible if information made available on this application is not accurate, complete or current. The material on this application is provided for general information only and should not be relied upon or used as the sole basis for making decisions without consulting primary, more accurate, more complete or more timely sources of information. Any reliance on the material on this application is at your own risk.\nThis application may contain certain historical information. Historical information, necessarily, is not current and is provided for your reference only. We reserve the right to modify the contents of this application at any time, but we have no obligation to update any information on our application. You agree that it is your responsibility to monitor changes to our application.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_modifications">4 - Modifications to the service and prices</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_modifications_description">Prices for our products are subject to change without notice. \nWe reserve the right at any time to modify or discontinue the Service (or any part or content thereof) without notice at any time. \nWe shall not be liable to you or to any third-party for any modification, price change, suspension or discontinuance of the Service. \nIf user selected wrong ECU in order, administrator will write about wrong selection in ticket for exact order and will notice about prices changes because of wrong ecu was selected. And if in selected priority time client not accepting that, admin have rights to finish order with correc selection orders options and prices.</string>
</resources>
